what's happening is is that the
magnitude of the risk is now existential
we can now kill everybody and the kinds
of things that are in that magnitude are
proliferating and the difficulty of
getting access to it is going down so
that arc is a very bad are your side of
this story which I buy by the would
completely agree with and believe in him
that's all I care about is focusing on
going there is that there's a mirror
image yeah that these same powers can be
used for good yes the difference I think
right now is that up until recently they
could be used for good now they must be
used for good yes which is which isn't
in kind of an imperative for us to
transcend to the level we need to get to
to become the species that we could be
you need those kind of stakes who's it
for hmm well like that in our direction
yeah yeah and in the old balance no
light without shadow etc and no hero
without the balanced VIP villain you
need that motivation to be greater and
to go further and to be a better version
of yourself and you know a better
version of all of us together because as
you've talked about it takes all of us
working way harder and making all of us
way better together to be able to combat
those things